export default {
  title: "ㅅ ㅆ",
  syllables: [
    {
      question: '삼',
options: "ㅅ ㅆ",
      answer: 'ㅅ'
    }, {
      question: '쌈',
options: "ㅅ ㅆ",
      answer: 'ㅆ'
    }, {
      question: '살',
options: "ㅅ ㅆ",
      answer: 'ㅅ'
    }, {
      question: '쌀',
options: "ㅅ ㅆ",
      answer: 'ㅆ'
    }, {
      question: '스',
options: "ㅅ ㅆ",
      answer: 'ㅅ'
    }, {
      question: '쓰',
options: "ㅅ ㅆ",
      answer: 'ㅆ'
    }, {
      question: '서',
options: "ㅅ ㅆ",
      answer: 'ㅅ'
    }, {
      question: '써',
options: "ㅅ ㅆ",
      answer: 'ㅆ'
    }, {
      question: '시',
options: "ㅅ ㅆ",
      answer: 'ㅅ'
    }, {
      question: '씨',
options: "ㅅ ㅆ",
      answer: 'ㅆ'
    }
  ]
}
